

□ (+82) 10-4126-1753 | Sigywonchung@snu.ac.kr | Aijaewonchung.me | Dijaywonchung

Summary _

I am a senior student majoring Electrical and Computer Engineering at Seoul National University, South Korea. I am interested in software systems that support deep learning, and also optimizing system components using deep learning. I have experience on GPU cluster resource management, server-client collaborative DNN inference, and meta-learning. I also try to follow up on state-of-the-art deep learning research during my free time.

Education

Seoul National University

Seoul, South Korea

B.S. STUDENT IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Mar 2015 - Aug 2021 (expected)

- Current GPA: 4.09/4.3 (overall) 4.15/4.3 (major)
- Period includes two years of social service, required to all Korean men.

Publications

• ShadowTutor: Distributed Partial Distillation for Mobile Video DNN Inference, <u>Jae-Won Chung</u>, Jae-Yun Kim, Soo-Mook Moon, 49th International Conference on Parallel Processing, 2020 (Acceptance rate = 29%)

Research Experience _____

Software Platform Lab

SNU, South Korea

RESEARCH INTERN

Apr 2020 - Present

- Advised by Professor Byung-Gon Chun.
- Working on Crane, an elastic GPU cluster resource manager for deep learning workloads.

Virtual Machine and Optimization Lab

SNU, South Korea

SENIOR PROJECT

Dec 2019 - Jun 2020

- Advised by Professor Soo-Mook Moon.
- Developed a novel a server-client collaborative video DNN inference scheme that drastically reduces network traffic via intermittent knowledge distillation.
- Implemented the scheme with PyTorch & OpenMPI and conducted evaluation using an NVIDIA Jetson Nano board as the client.

Computer Vision Lab

SNU, South Korea
Jun 2019 - Dec 2019

RESEARCH INTERN

- · Advised by Professor Kyoung Mu Lee.
- Accumulated experience in Meta-learning and Few-shot Classification.
- Conducted research on better meta-initialization points for Model-Agnostic Meta-Learning (MAML) using an LSTM-based neural memory.
- · Conducted research on generating task-aware class embeddings to augment feature maps of MAML with a convex program (DPP).

Lab of Imaging Science and Technology

SNU, South Korea

RESEARCH INTERN

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

- Advised by Professor Jongho Lee.
- Developed deep Learning methods for Quantitative Susceptibility Mapping (QSM)
- · Designed, implemented, and trained a U-Net variant on in-vivo brain MRI field images and their COSMOS results.
- Submitted our solution to the QSM challenge held by the 5th International Workshop on MRI Phase Contrast and QSM.

Honors & Awards

Mar 2019 Kwanjeong Undergraduate Scholarship, Kwanjeong Educational Foundation

Seoul, South Korea

Extracurricular Activity _____

Deepest deepest.ai

• A free research group on all domains of deep learning. Aggregates researchers from both academia and industry with various backgrounds.

- Gained experience extensively in computer vision and meta-learning, and attended talks on computer vision, natural language processing, reinforcement learning, and speech recognition.
- Gave a talk with the title "Meta-Learning plus Memory".

Coursera Global Translator Community

translate-coursera.org

LANGUAGE COORDINATOR

MEMBER

Oct 2018 - Present

Dec 2018 - Present

- An official Coursera community that translates Coursera lecture subtitles.
- Served as Language Coordinator, a selected position that reviews and confirms works by other translators.
- · Created Korean subtitles for Coursera Lectures initially provided only in English. Focused on courses related to machine learning.

Teaching _____

• Fall 2020 Computer Organization (Undergraduate architecture), Peer tutor, provided 30 hours of online lecture

Skills _____

Languages Python (including asyncio), C, Verilog, Shell, C++, Go, Rust **Frameworks** PyTorch, NumPy, Matplotlib, Pillow, CUDA, OpenCV, OpenMPI

Tools Commandline, LaTeX, MATLAB

English TOEFL 120 (Perfect score, Feb 2020), TOEIC 990 (Perfect score, Oct 2018), GRE 167/170/4.5 (Mar 2018)